Office of the Vice Provost Records UA166
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA166.003; 46.8 Linear Feet
  - August 2017 accession, ORA Award files, circa 1986 -- 2014; UA166.003.002; 21 Linear Feet
    - 000381-00001, 2003 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - 001732-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - 002966-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - 003582-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - 003558-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - 002751-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - 002411-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - 003307-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - 002951-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - 003065-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - 003052-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - 002682-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - 002176-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - 002440-00001, 2005 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - 002125-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - 003279-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - 001766-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - 002487-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - 003658-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - 003276-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - 003038-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - 002929-00001, 2007 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - 003251-00001, 2005 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 25)
    - 001870-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 26)
    - 001789-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 27)
    - 002394-00001, 2010-- 2013; UA166.003.190.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 28)
    - 002328-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 29)
    - 003042-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 30)
    - 003516-00001, 2006 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 31)
    - 001786-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 32)
    - 003273-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - 003219-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - 003293-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - 001799-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - 002936-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - 002056-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - 003703-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - 001734-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - 003456-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - 002103-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - 002416-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - 001867-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - 002276-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - 002385-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - 002439-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - 003354-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - 003352-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - 001740-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.191.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - 002778-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 19)
    - 002805-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 20)
    - 002801-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 21)
    - 003085-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 22)
    - 003102-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 23)
    - 003598-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 24)
    - 002364-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 25)
    - 003205-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 26)
    - 002282-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 27)
    - 001655-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 28)
    - 003383-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 29)
    - 002968-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.191.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 30)
    - 002094-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.191.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 191, Folder 31)
    - 003370-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - 002294-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - 003187-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - 003146-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.192.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - 002507-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.192.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - 002683-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.192.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - 002860-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.192.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - 002192-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - 002925-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.192.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - 002618-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - 003445-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - 002643-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - 002286-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - 002209-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - 001971-00001, 2006 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - 002902-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - 003083-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - 003272-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - 003029-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - 003015-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.192.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 20)
    - 003192-00001, 2006 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 21)
    - 003487-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.192.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 22)
    - 003193-00001, 2009 -- 2014; UA166.003.192.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 23)
    - 003242-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 24)
    - 002210-00001, 2000 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 25)
    - 002296-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.192.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 26)
    - 000936-00001, 2008 -- 2014; UA166.003.192.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 27)
    - 003466-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.192.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 192, Folder 28)
    - 003466-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - 003120-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - 002587-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - 002857-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - 003509-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - 002619-00001, 1995 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - 003301-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - 002859-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - 002534-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - 100135-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - 002424-00001, 2011 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - 002612-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - 002613-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - 002779-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - 002776-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - 003023-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - 002775-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - 003119-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 18)
    - 001049-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 19)
    - 002414-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 20)
    - 003196-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 21)
    - 100256-00001, 2014 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 22)
    - 002410-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 23)
    - 002730-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 24)
    - 100109-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 25)
    - 002447-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 26)
    - 002360-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 27)
    - 002530-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 28)
    - 002535-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 29)
    - 002622-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 30)
    - 100186-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 31)
    - 100213-00001, 2014 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 32)
    - 002023-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 33)
    - 002073-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 34)
    - 003099-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 35)
    - 002492-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.193.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 36)
    - 003265-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 37)
    - 002969-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.193.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 193, Folder 38)
    - 003438-00001, 2011-- 2013; UA166.003.194.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - 003518-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - 002284-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - 002285-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - 002799-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - 002353-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - 003194-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - 002002-00001, 2007 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - 002150-00001, 2008 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - 001634-00001, 1986 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - 002882-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - 002924-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - 002288-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - 002283-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - 003515-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - 002526-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - 002323-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - 002789-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - 001876-00001, 2003 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 19)
    - 003180-00001, 2009 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 20)
    - 002949-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 21)
    - 100156-00001, 2014 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 22)
    - 001855-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.194.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 23)
    - 003121-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.194.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 194, Folder 24)
    - 001725-00001, 1995 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - 100066-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - 003532-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - 002405-00001, 2011 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - 002551-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - 002485-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - 002632-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - 002790-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - 002490-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - 001085-00001, 2007 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - 002560-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - 002856-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - 002558-00001, 2011 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - 001774-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - 003422-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - 001201-00001, 1993 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - 002842-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - 002453-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - 002482-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - 002529-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - 002528-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - 002559-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 22)
    - 002633-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 23)
    - 002819-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 24)
    - 002913-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 25)
    - 002679-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 26)
    - 001886-00001, 2009 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 27)
    - 003411-00001, 2008 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 28)
    - 003289-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.195.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 29)
    - 003435-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.195.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 195, Folder 30)
    - 001184-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - 001670-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - 002287-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - 003159-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - 002736-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - 003439-00001, 1989 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - 001923-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - 002512-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - 003467-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - 003523-00001, 2002 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - 001179-00001, 2008 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - 003002-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - 003073-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - 003133-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - 001222-00001, 1986 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - 002571-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - 002376-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - 003138-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - 003143-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - 002702-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - 002616-00001, 2012 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - 003013-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.196.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - 003005-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.196.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - 003203-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.197.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 1)
      Accessions
      UA-2018-029
    - 003234-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.197.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - 002982-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.197.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 3)
      Ua-2018-029
    - 003416-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.197.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - 100216-00001, 2014; UA166.003.197.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - 100134-00001, 2013 -- 2014; UA166.003.197.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Box 6)
    - 001817-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.197.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - 002010-00001, 2010 -- 2014; UA166.003.197.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - 003267-00001, 2011 -- 2014; UA166.003.197.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - 002844-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.197.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - December 2017 accession, Medford grant files, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.003; 12.6 Linear Feet
    Transferred by Jonathan Chau, Office of the Vice Provost, 2017, accession UA-2018-031.
    This subseries is arranged in received order.
    This subseries contains grant files from the Medford campus from 2010-2016.
    - 001727-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 11)
      UA-2018-031
    - 002695-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - 001129-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - 001720-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - 001729-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - 002030-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - 002279-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - 002345-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - 002463-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - 002494-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - 002690-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - 002764-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - 002868-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - 002908-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - 002920-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - 003097-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 26)
    - 003149-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 27)
    - 003155-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 28)
    - 003198-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 29)
    - 003214-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 30)
    - 003240-00001, 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.197.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 197, Folder 31)
    - 003329-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - 003331-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - 003404-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - 003512-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - 003631-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - 001659-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - 002272-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - 003264-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - 003375-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - 002768-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - 003389-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - 100024-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - 002647-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - 003418-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - 002370-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - 002660-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - 003286-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.198.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - 100070-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - 002503-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - 002895-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - 100093-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - 000938-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - 002685-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - 002343-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - 002197-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - 003212-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - 003323-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - 003182-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.199.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - 001646-00001, circa 2010 -- 2016; UA166.003.200.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 200, Folder 1)